<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" encoding="UTF-8" href="iform.xsl" version="1.0"?>

<!DOCTYPE textsection PUBLIC "-//ARM//DTD textsection //EN" "iform-p.dtd">

<textsection title="Proprietary Notice">
  <para>
    This document is protected by copyright and other related rights
and the practice or implementation of the information contained in
this document may be protected by one or more patents or pending
patent applications. No part of this document may be reproduced in any
form by any means without the express prior written permission of ARM
Limited (“ARM”). <b>No license, express or implied, by estoppel or
otherwise to any intellectual property rights is granted by this
document unless specifically stated.</b>
  </para>
  <para>
    Your access to the information in this document is conditional
upon your acceptance that you will not use or permit others to use the
information for the purposes of determining whether implementations
infringe any patents.
  </para>
  <para>
    THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED “AS IS”. ARM PROVIDES NO REPRESENTATIONS
AND NO WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, WITHOUT
LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY
QUALITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE WITH
RESPECT TO THE DOCUMENT. For the avoidance of doubt, ARM makes no
representation with respect to, and has undertaken no analysis to
identify or understand the scope and content of, third party patents,
copyrights, trade secrets, or other rights.
  </para>
  <para>
    This document may include technical inaccuracies or typographical
errors.
  </para>
  <para>
    TO THE EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL ARM BE
LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY DIRECT,
INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES,
HOWEVER CAUSED AND REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT
OF ANY USE OF THIS DOCUMENT, EVEN IF ARM HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
  </para>
  <para>
This document consists solely of commercial items. You shall be
responsible for ensuring that any use, duplication or disclosure of
this document complies fully with any relevant export laws and
regulations to assure that this document or any portion thereof is not
exported, directly or indirectly, in violation of such export
laws. Use of the word “partner” in reference to ARM’s customers is not
intended to create or refer to any partnership relationship with any
other company. ARM may make changes to this document at any time and
without notice.
  </para>
  <para>
If any of the provisions contained in these terms conflict with any of
the provisions of any signed written agreement specifically covering
this document with ARM, then the signed written agreement prevails
over and supersedes the conflicting provisions of these terms.
  </para>
  <para>
Words and logos marked with &#174; or &#8482; are registered
trademarks or trademarks of ARM Limited or its affiliates in the EU
and/or elsewhere. All rights reserved. Other brands and names
mentioned in this document may be the trademarks of their respective
owners. You must follow the ARM trademark usage guidelines
<url>http://www.arm.com/about/trademarks/guidelines/index.php</url>.
  </para>
  <para>
    Copyright &#169; 2017 ARM Limited or its affiliates. All rights
reserved.
  </para>
  <para>
    ARM Limited. Company 02557590 registered in England.
  </para>
  <para>
    110 Fulbourn Road, Cambridge, England CB1 9NJ.
  </para>
  <para>
    LES-PRE-20327
  </para>
  <para>
    In this document, where the term ARM is used to refer to the
company it means “ARM or any of its subsidiaries as appropriate”.
  </para>
</textsection>
